Okay. So, how do you access um something
from your promise? We've created two
promises here. Um and we want to access
them. Um so, what I'm going to do is I'm
going to actually console
log promise so that you can see it the
one that we just created on line 17 so
that you can see what it returns. So if
we do that and we go live,
theoretically it will go live at some
point. Okay, here we are. And if we go
to our console, um you can see here it
returns a promise. And if you open it
up, it says promise. And then it says
the promise was fulfilled and it
returned hello world. That's what's
going to be returned. So this could be
asynchronous code and it could take a
long time to run. And so then this would
just say it was a promise. So, for
example, let's make this take 10 times
as long and we'll reload our page. We
have a promise that's pending. It's
undefined. So, when we console.logged
it, it was in the pending state. We
don't yet have the result of it. It's
pending. So, how do you access the
results? Well, what you can do is just
like a string has built-in attributes
likelit.
two uppercase promises also have
built-in attributes and functions that
you can call. So if I wanted to call a
function here, I could say promise
then. The dot then function is a
built-in function to promises and it
allows you to take the result of the
promise once it's been resolved. In
other words, it allows you to wait until
your code is done running and then print
out the value. So it what it takes in as
a param as an input is it takes in a
function. That function receives a value
and the value is going to be what's
returned from your promise. So up here
where we're resolving it with hello
world that is what's going to go into
value. If we change this to resolving
with 1 2 3 then it would resolve with 1
2 3 and that would go into value. And so
your function needs to take in that
parameter and then it needs to do
something with it. So here we could
console.blog not log the value. So if we
save that and we come over here and we
reload.
Oh yeah, I'm having it wait 10 seconds
before it does that. I'm going to go
change that. Let's have that wait
3 seconds. So if we save that and we
come over here, we can look at our
console. One, two, three. And there's
our hello world. And we're good to go.
So that is how you can have a promise.
You can set it up to delay code a
certain amount of time or if you're
waiting for something to come back from
the internet to wait till something
comes back from the internet and then
you can say once it does take the value
and do something with it. Um, and we'll
continue that in the next